Michael V. Brock

Snoqualmie, WA 98065 mikebrock.me github.com/mbrock76 linkedin.com/in/mbrock76

Professional Summary

Software developer with experience and training in data analysis, full stack web applications, and scripting. Experience creating and analyzing systems in diverse industries, extracting insights to improve processes and productivity. Familiarity with web development using JS, React, Java and PHP. Experienced manager of employees and processes in production environments.

Skills

HTML • CSS • JS • React • PHP • Java • Python • SQL • Tableau • MS Office suite

Professional Experience

Aston Carter, remote Financial Services Rep. Nov 2022 to present

Investigate financial requests from consumers, adjust records accordingly.

Revature, remote Software Developer Feb 2022 to Jul 2022

- Completed the Revature training program for full stack developer with a focus on spring and react
- Continued to sharpen skills in remote staging while interviewing with clients.

Microconnex, Snoqualmie, WA Laser Technician/programmer Oct 2017 to Aug 2021

- Developed python scripts to gather data from production machines and process the data into a universal format for visualization
- Created a system involving python to automate serialization setup for production
- Implemented a system using python to duplicate production to consume full sheets of material, greatly increasing productivity
- Developed web applications for operators to view supporting documentation on tablets, as well as usage data
- Programmed VMS machines for Automated Optical Inspection of circuits
- Created fixtures to improve processes

Education

NEW Apprenticeship, remote Data Analyst Aug 2022 to Oct 2022

Completed the Data Analyst training cohort for SQL, Tableau, and python.

ITT Tech, Louisville, KY A.A.S. Jun 2009 to Sep 2011

- Earned an Associates of Applied Science degree in Software Applications Programming
- received dean's highest honors for attendance, a GPA of 3.8, and was accepted into the National Honors Society